美国经济崩溃  失业率为21.6% 创下新高
犯罪猖獗 警察无力抵挡  犯罪率急剧上升 达到历史最高水平
腐败和暴力充斥着许多城市
政府行使土地征用权 建立高大的围墙  将138平方英里的废弃厂房区域用围墙围起来
政府指派维兰德国际公司承包监狱相关业务  它管理着全世界最大的私人监狱"混乱王国"
犯人们崇尚一种残忍的竞技运动"死亡飞车"  开着车辆互相残杀 以争得"混乱王国"的统治权  这不仅仅是一项竞技运动 还是一种生活方式
控制区 围墙
大家认为死亡飞车会一直进行下去
政府已宣布死亡飞车是非法的
再见了 混蛋
Sayonara, motherfucker!
准备开始行动 你能检查一下吗
We're going live. Can you check on it?
十辆车已毁 还剩两辆
Ten cars down, two to go.
这些驾驶员真是疯了
These drivers are crazy.
我还是不明白 为什么这些人都愿意去死呢
I still don't understand why they are so willing to die.
因为所有人都想当上那儿的老大
Because everyone wants to be king of the hill.
- 已经开始在暗网播放比赛视频了吗 - 是的 监狱长
- Is it already streaming on the dark web? - Yes, warden.
正在I2P匿名网络和Tor网络上实况直播
It is online in real time on Freenet, I2P, and Tor.
难道没有办法利用网络攻击追踪到服务商 并关闭它们吗
There is no way to trace the ISP and shut 'em down with a web based attack?
如果我是国安局的 或许给我几个月的时间能搞定
If I was the NSA and had a couple months, maybe.
这些家伙是非法的网络武装分子
These guys are illegitimate cyber militia.
加密技术是一流的 十秒钟改变一次
The encryption is first ray, it's bouncing every 10 seconds.
那就切断他们的电力供应
Then kill their power.
他们没有使用外部供电
We don't supply their powering.
他们用的是自己的发电机网络
They are on their own generator grid.
干掉这狗娘养的
Take out this motherfucker.
干得漂亮
Yeah baby!
去你妈的 弗兰克
Fuck you, Frank!
现在切换到22号摄像头
Right now, get us in the 22.
OTP赌博网站那边有消息了么
Any word from the OTP site?
许多人已经下注了 OTP网站和在线投注金额正在上升
On site and the online waging are up. They are writing a lot of betting slips.
向另一位赛车手投注了大量现金
The house is banking cash on the secondary racers
还有人连本带利的赌 我们今天玩得有点大
and the parlays, and we are wrecking in some big.
弗兰克斯坦赢了 可就要赚翻了
Frankenstein wins... There is a payout.
死亡飞车是非法的 现在规模空前的大
Death race is illegal and bigger than ever.
感谢我们的这位疯子弗兰克
Thanks to our resident crazy man Frank.
去他妈的 弗兰克斯坦
Ah... Fuck Frankenstein,
是你让死亡飞车比赛起死回生
You are the one who resurrected Death race from the dead.
我只是想明白了如何译解卫星信号
I just figured out how to decode the satellite
并通过暗网直播比赛
signals and stream it on the dark web.
因为有了我们 弗兰克斯坦才得以重生
Frankenstein has been born again, thanks to us.
如果他今晚赢了的话 他就七连胜了
Oh... If he wins tonight, it'll be his the seventh straight.
外面的联络人说我们的利润正在降低
Oh, our contacts on the outside says our margins are dropping
因为没有人愿意给另一方下注
because nobody's taking the other side of the bet.
因为弗兰克斯坦我们要丢很多钱了
We are losing a lot of money on Frankenstein.
我们得让比赛更加惊险
We need to spice things up.
那些连本带利的赌徒都赚翻了 但是…
The parlays are paying off, but...
我们需要一位挑战者
We need a challenger.
特警正在路上 五分钟后抵达
SWAT is on en route, T minus five minutes.
让我们这次彻底终结弗兰克斯坦和死亡飞车比赛吧
Let's shut Frankenstein and Death race down once and for all.
外面有动静了
We've got some action from the outside.
你不是想刺激一点么 现在特警来了
You wanted to spice. Say hello to SWAT.
追上 撞烂他们
Let's trace and pinch him.
舔我吧 弗兰克
Suck my dick, Frankie!
也来舔我 弗兰克
Same my dick too, Frankie!
去他的 把他们撞在墙上
Push them into the fucking wall!
来啊
Do it baby!
去他的
Mother fucker!
- 想办法出来 - 混蛋
- Get off the wall! - Damn it!
干掉这混蛋
Take this motherfucker out!
我选错了司机
I picked the wrong driver!
《死亡飞车4：混乱之上》
两张一样 两张八加三张A
Full house. Eight over Aces.
不错 两张九加三张J
Nice. Nines over jacks.
我要把我的钱拿回来
I'd like a shot at getting my money back.
我今晚去你那儿怎么样
Why don't I come to your place later tonight?
说不定我们能再玩玩牌呢
Maybe we can shuffle another deck of cards.
不错啊
Esta bien.
嘿 老大 我这有一位客人
Hey Jefe, I have got a player
想赌点大的
who wants to play some heavy action.
赌特警与弗兰克斯坦谁会赢
On SWAT vs Frankenstein.
- 特警 - 特警
- SWAT? - SWAT.
他赌多少
Who is gonna play his money?
十万押特警赢 两边可能性持平吧
SWAT for a hundred thousand. Even odds.
我押另外一边吧
My book. I'll fit the odd.
赔率3:1
Three to one,
如果他敢不玩的话
and if he gives you any push back,
就告诉他 墨西哥老犹太说 滚回家跟你妈一起去死吧
tell him that Mexican Jew said, go to hell and take his mom.
希望他收到了上次给他送的枪
I hope they got their last shipment of guns.
现在帮我赢笔钱吧 弗兰克
Now make me some money, Frank.
弗兰克斯坦 弗兰克斯坦
Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein...
前进
Forward.
去左边 安全
To the left. All clear!
一区 安全
Clear, sector one.
突入组 行动
Breach team, move out.
快快快
Go, go, go!
停
Hold up!
- 看住后面 - 上上
- Back it up. - Go, go!
里面有没有摄像头
Tell me we got cameras in there?
有啊 到处都布下了摄像头
Yeah, we have got cameras everywhere.
往左边
Go left.
左边 安全
Left, clear.
往右边
Go right.
右边 安全
Go right, clear.
两位目标 倒下
Two tango down!
二区 请报告
Sector two, report.
收到 指挥部
Copy that Foreman.
队员 继续前进
Spec ops, move.
什么也没有发现
Got eyes on nothing.
混蛋 我们上
Yeah motherfuckers, let's go.
我们赢了
Now we get a little!
监狱长 把你最好的手下都派过来吧
Send me the best you got warden,
我会把他们扒皮
I'll send them back to you skinned,
分尸 掏出内脏 再送回去的
gutted and quartered.
外面的世界可能你能控制 但这是我的地盘
You may be in charge out there, but this is my city.
这里是混乱王国
This is the Sprawl!
避开第一个角落
Get around the first corner.
什么事
Hello?
这消息要是上了明天的华盛顿时报可不太妙
This isn't gonna play well in the Washington Post tomorrow.
我知道 瓦伦丁先生
I know, Mr Valentine.
你也知道国会的人
Well, then you know that I got Congress
逼问我混乱王国的情况 还讨论了一些道德问题
at my ass about the Sprawl and its morality.
弗兰克斯坦已经失去控制了
Frankenstein is out of control,
他的军队日渐壮大
his legion is growing.
政府要把监狱控制权收回去
The government is gonna take back my prison
除非我们现在就能搞定弗兰克斯坦
unless we shut down Frankenstein, and shutting down now!
当我接管维兰德国际的时候
When I took over Weyland International
我接到了一项非常明确的命令
I was tasked with a very specific directive.
清理混乱王国 终结弗兰克斯坦
Clean up the Sprawl and put an end to Frankenstein.
更重要的是 要取缔死亡飞车
More importantly, Death race.
我们的合同已经签了五年了 我们也往那个
Our contracts up in five years, and we got a
人渣堆投了不少钱
lot of invest in that human garbage dump.
所以 如果我被迫参加这个国会监督委员会会议
So when I get pulled in to a congressional oversight committee
我要怎么解释给这435位议员听
what should I say to the 435 members of the house?
告诉他们我们正在尽力解决 但是
Well, tell them that we're doing our best, but...
但是什么 我们控制不住这帮神经病罪犯
But what? We can't control a bunch of sociopath gear heads,
弗兰克斯坦成了传奇人物
and Frankenstein is even more legendary
死亡飞车比赛是非法的
now the Death Race is illegal?
- 我能搞定弗兰克斯坦的 先生 - 真的吗
- I can handle Frankenstein, sir. - Really?
因为就我来看
Cause from where I see,
弗兰克斯坦的所作所为让你看起来像个蠢货
Frankenstein is making you look like a chump.
他手下的人差不多已经算得上一只小型军队了
He's gathering his team amounting what adds up to a small army.
你从外部是搞不定他的
You can't shut him down from the outside.
他只不过是个戴面具的人罢了 谁戴面具都可以
He's just a mask. Anybody can wear the mask.
得让他的追随者 无论内外都必须看到他屈辱的失败
His disciples, inside and out, need to see him suffer, humiliate in the feet.
我们得让他死亡飞车比赛时身亡 而且要死的很惨
He needs to die during Death Race, and die bloody.
他要是输掉了死亡飞车比赛 就会丢掉权力
He loses Death Race, he loses his power.
这就是我们夺回监狱控制权的办法
That's how you take back our prison.
你搞定这事 要不然我自己动手
Make it happen or I will.
我现在要告诉你们一些不太妙的消息
What I'm about to feed you is going to taste bitter.
你们会发现自己永远赢不了
You have found yourself in a no win situation.
只有两种情况 生或者死
There are two options! Die or survive.
不会给你们提供衣服
You will not be given clothes.
你们现在穿的是什么 以后穿的就是什么
What you're wearing is what you'll wear.
不会给你们睡觉地方
You will not be given a place to sleep,
什么都不会给你们
you will not be given jack shit,
可能什么时候脑袋上给你来一枪
except maybe a bullet in the brain!
如果你足够幸运的话 尽管放心
If you are lucky, rest assured,
围墙内没有处女
there are no virgins within these walls,
因为生活会把你们彻彻底底的蹂躏一顿
because life has fucked you all.
混乱王国占地88000英亩 这里会发生很多屁事
The sprawl is 88,000 acres of bad shit about to happen.
控制区的牢房内关押着42万名
The containment zone warehouses 420,000 of the worst...
罪大恶极的犯人
of the worst offenders.
给你们最好的建议是 学会逃命 学会战斗
Best advice, learn how to run. Learn how to fight!
别盯着我了 混蛋
Stop eye fucking me, asshole.
政府决定提供给你们一管银币
Uncle Sam, has decided to provide you with one roll of silver coin.
在围墙之内 这就是通用的货币
This will be your currency inside the walls!
这真是废话
That's the hogwash!
现在都准备好 我们马上降落
Now, get yourselves ready, we are approaching alpha bravo.
去啊 犯人们 快去
Go convicts, go, go!
让这里的世界更美好 赶紧他妈的滚出去
Make the world a better place! Get the fuck out of here!
要怎么参加 死亡飞车
How do I get in Death Race?
去找巴尔的摩·鲍勃 满足了他想要的 就会让你参赛的
Find Baltimore Bob. If you got what it takes, he will get you in.
快点 快点下飞机
Move, get off my bird now!
走
Go!
你在看什么呢 快点走
What are you staring at? Come on!
谁想来过几招
Who wants to play?
过来 你这混蛋
Come here, you mother...
跪下
On your knees!
他妈的跪下
Get the fuck on the ground.
这什么狗屁
What is this shit?
闭上你的臭嘴 不准盯着我看
Shut your fucking mouth! Quit eyeballing me!
这不是一位美女一位丑男么
Well, ain't this a rainbow, or a fucking ugly?
- 你们迷路了 - 我们很好
- You folks lost? - We're good.
你们看起来迷路了
You look lost.
我们很好 谢谢
No, we're good. Thanks.
你们很好
You are good?
挺好的
It's good.
你他妈的把银币交出来
Now give me your fucking silver.
为什么要给你
Why would we do that?
这个叫入境税
It's a landing tax.
为什么你不直接把我们打死了 自己拿呢
Why don't you just shoot us and take it?
说不定我只是不想把我的子弹
Maybe I don't wanna waste my bullets
浪费在你这样的臭婊子身上呢
on a gutter bitch like you.
你还挺能说会道的啊
You are a real sweet talker. Ain't you?
谢谢夸奖
Thanks, I try.
我不觉得枪里面有子弹
I don't think you have any bullets.
其实
In fact,
我觉得你打的都是空包弹
I think you are shooting blanks.
行啊
Okay.
你们想来硬的
You folks wanna play it the hard way?
都他妈的靠卡车站好
Up against the fucking truck!
你就是想这样吗
Is this what you wanted?
我现在感觉不太妙 我欠了你一个人情啊
I got this bad feeling, I owe you pretty boy.
我们扯平了
We are square.
你就是揍了警察的那个家伙吗
You the one, that gave the cops a beating?
我不想惹什么乱子
I don't want any trouble.
是么
Oh, you don't?
你要是教训了警察 那你就惹上乱子了
Because if you tuned up the cops, you are gonna have some.
我只是在找巴尔的摩·鲍勃
I'm just looking for Baltimore Bob.
上车吧 小子
Jump in, cowboy.
我开车送你去
I'll give you a ride.
去你的 混蛋
Fuck you, asshole.
滚开 提利
Fuck off, 'Tilly.
如果我有那玩意儿 我就要塞你屁眼里
If I had a dick, here is what I tell your ass to suck it.
所以你是说 一个人赤手空拳
So your story, is that one unarmed man
打倒了你和你的手下
took out you and your gang,
还抢走了我的入境税款
and pushed in my landing tax?
抱歉 弗兰克 我下次会做的更好的
I'm sorry, Frank. I'll do better next time.
混乱王国没有下次 你懂这个道理的
There is no next time here in the Sprawl, you know this.
你杀了警察被送这儿 现在你连一个小喽啰都搞不定
You got sad here for killing cops, and you can't handle one con?
我说了 抱歉 弗兰克 我下次会做的更好的
Like I said, I am sorry Frank. I'll do better next time.
他只是运气好而已
He just got lucky.
你收的每一块银币 都要上缴给混乱王国
Every piece of silver you collect, goes right back to the Sprawl.
收不上税的话 这地盘就要吃苦头了
When my landing tax goes uncollected, the city suffers.
你想吃苦头么
Do you like to suffer?
我不想吃苦头 弗兰克
I don't like to suffer, Frank.
就是他 就是那个混蛋
That's him. That's the mother fucker!
- 嘿 贝克丝 - 这家伙在找巴尔的摩·鲍勃
- Hey, Bex. - This guy is looking for Baltimore Bob.
一眼就能看出来
'Course he is.
康纳·吉布森 这位是简
Connor Gibson, meet Jane.
很高兴见到你 简
It's good to meet you, Jane.
就交给你了 小妞
He is all yours, chica.
我要去跳跳舞了
I'mma go dance on the pole.
所以
So,
你是从哪来的
where's you moving from?
长岛
Long Beach.
你是怎么进来的
What are you in it for?
这重要吗
Does it matter?
对我来说挺重要的
Does, for me.
我就是来了这 没什么原因 跟大家没什么两样
I'm here because I'm here, just like everyone else.
我的一位收税员告诉我 你袭击并抢走了他身上的钱
One of my tax collectors told me you attacked him and then robbed him.
事情并不是这样的
It's not exactly how it went down.
那讲给我听啊 犯人
Enlighten me, convict.
杀了他 弗兰克
Kill him Frank!
你的一位手下和他的同伙们图谋不轨
Your boy and his pals tried to jump me.
可你还是好好的啊
Yet you're the one who walked away.
我又没说他们得手了
I didn't say they were any good on it.
让我揍他 弗兰克
Let me whack him Frank.
他只不过是他爸
He's nothing but a couple of drops of
射了一个路边妓女生出来的罢了
sprouted from a shit filled crack in the sidewalk.
我们以前见过面吗
Have we met before?
我不这么觉得 我是新来的
I don't think so. I just got here.
就算以前见过 我也不知道 你躲在面具后面呢
And if we had, I wouldn't know. You're hiding behind a mask.
这是我的地盘
This is my city.
不准有人这么跟我说话
No one speaks to me like that.
杀了那个混蛋
Kill that motherfucker!
听着 你说我偷了东西 我什么也没偷
Listen, you accuse me of stealing, and I didn't steal anything.
我为我自己辩护
I defended myself.
你的手下自己挑事 又打不过 这不是我的错
It's not my fault your boys weren't up to the fight they picked.
小心了 犯人
Watch your back convict.
你绝对不是从长岛来的
You're definitely not from Long Beach.
你似乎习惯于挑战比你强太多的人啊 犯人
You're making a habit to punch above your weight... Convict!
听说你在找我
Word is, you're looking for me.
你是巴尔的摩·鲍勃
Baltimore Bob?
你真是吃了熊心豹子胆啊
Your balls must be made out of titanium.
我从来没见过有人敢那么跟弗兰克说话
I've never seen anyone talk to Frank like that.
你会开车吗
You drive?
我会开车
Yeah, I drive.
你是怎么进来的 鲍勃
So, what are you in here for, Bob?
就说是因为我帮助别人离开这个世界吧
Let's just say I help people transition.
那些媒体称我为"杀人博士"
Press called me Dr Kill.
我是一位肿瘤学家
I was an oncologist.
是啊 我读过关于你的报道
Yeah, I read about you.
你给400位垂死之人做了安乐死手术
You euthanize 400 dying people.
432位 他们并非全是垂死之人
Yeah, 432, and not all of 'em were dying.
有些人微不足道
Some were living inconsequential lives,
跟死了没什么两样
and in as such they were already dead.
快点 快点
Come on, come on!
上那卡车
Get the truck!
这食物归弗兰克斯坦所有
The food is property of Frankenstein!
他们在干什么
What the hell are they doing?
食物抢劫时间
Feeding time.
他们是弗兰克的追随者
Disciples of Frank.
他们抢劫食物运输车 控制食物供给量
They hijack the food shipments and control the supply.
让人们饿肚子 这样更易于控制
If you keep the populous hungry they are easy to control.
那些武器和赛车都是从哪里来的
Where do all the weapons and cars come from?
手工制造 自己动手 我们会利用各种各样的破烂零件
Handmade, home-made, we lick the bottom of the pad.
外面送什么我们就用什么
And we furbish whatever sticks to our tongues.
有送好东西这些人都拿不到
They never get a bit fat from outside.
离那些肉远点 你们这帮混蛋
Keep away from the meat, all your motherfucker!
去死吧 狗娘养的
Die, motherfucker!
该死的 独裁狂
Fuck you, Nazi fuck!
你就是大家议论纷纷的那个家伙
You are the one everybody's talking about?
消息传的很快啊
News travels fast huh?
毕竟这地方规模不大
Small town, really.
准确的说有二十二万六千人
Two hundred and twenty six thousand to be exact.
我们这每年有一万九千人死掉
We have about 19,000 deaths a year and...
两万两千人从外面送进来
22000 come over the wall.
抱歉 我又念叨这些数据了
Sorry, I'm doing it again.
康纳·吉布森 这位是百事通
Connor Gibson, meet Lists.
所以我们这是在看什么
So what am I watching here?
他们是非死亡飞车参赛者 在竞争参赛席位
It where the non-racers compete for a spot in Death race.
如何赢得席位
How do you get a spot?
你要在"你死我活"中胜出
You have to win the Death Match.
《你死我活》现在开始
Let the Death Match begin!
我们要介绍的第一位参赛者 来自纽约城
Our first contestant is all the way from New York City, New York.
她是杀手 窃贼 一位性感的小婊子
She's a killer and a thief, and one sexy little bitch of F.
有请吉普赛·萝丝
Give it up for Gipsy Rose!
下一位 他的家乡遍布玉米地和鸡粪
Next up, born in the tall corn and chicken
他来自密西西比州 牛津
droppings of Oxford, Mississippi,
- 这位是精神病… - 那女主持人是什么来头
- We have a psychotic... - Who is the girl?
弗兰克的女朋友
Frank's main squeeze.
你懂的 就是那种标准的性感模特
You know, standard guard and parade pleasure model.
卡丽·杰朵儿 这是她的艺名
Carley J'adore, it's her stage name.
她因17起贩卖人口案
She was charged with 17 counts of human trafficking,
8起卖淫案 5起非法拘禁案 受到指控
eight counts prostitution, and another five counts of false imprisonment.
她以前是拉拉队队长
She is an ex cheerleader.
色情影星
Ex porn star.
没错
Exactly.
工作从未离开过色情
Never did a day's work vertical.
各就各位
On your mark,
准备开始 你死我活
Get set, and die!
杀 杀
Kill, kill!
我听不见欢呼声
I can't hear you!
闭上你的
Shut your fucking...
不要自以为自己有点本事
Don't pick a fight with Godzilla
就去挑衅比你强大的人
because you think you know how to throw a punch.
你考虑一晚上吧
Sleep on it.
你明天还想参加死亡飞车
You still want Death Race tomorrow?
我们再谈
We'll talk.
嘿 长岛来的小子
Hey, Long Beach.
我这有酒 也许你需要人陪陪
Got a bottle. Could use some company.
- 这里不错啊 - 谢谢
- Nice in here. - Thanks.
开门见山的问吧 这儿的人都会开口问的
Go ahead and ask. Everybody always asks.
在这地方那话就类似于"你属什么星座"
It's kind of like the "what's your star sign" line in here.
我有罪
I'm guilty.
我并不打算问你这个
I wasn't gonna ask.
你不说我也会知道的
Yeah, which I would've found out anyway.
混乱王国没有秘密可言
There's no secret here in this Sprawl.
我以前嫁给了一位很不错的人
I married a really great guy,
后来发现他其实并不怎么样
who turned out to be not such a great guy.
他殴打了我几次
He beat me up a couple of times.
我原谅了他
I forgave him.
经济崩溃了 他丢了工作
The market crashed, he lost his job,
打我的次数越来越频繁了
smacked me around a bit more.
我还是原谅了他
I forgave him again.
然后有一天
And then one day,
我选择不原谅他了
I didn't forgive him.
我打了他九枪
I shot him nine times.
你知道吗 我其实还有点后悔
You know my one regret though?
后悔我没有打他十枪
That I didn't shoot the bastard ten.
你还想跟我继续交往吗
Do you still wanna not boots with me?
我没有说我不想啊
I never said I didn't.
行的
Okay.
我不想留着这酒
Wasn't really out for the taking anyway.
只想找个人陪我喝了而已
I just needed somebody to finish this bottle with.
而你
and you're,
是某个来自长岛的神秘男子吧
some... mysterious guy from Long Beach, right?
我去睡一会儿
Get some sleep.
你想睡的话 可以睡沙发
Couch is yours if you want it.
欢迎来到温室
Welcome to the Green house.
这是巴尔的摩·鲍勃的杰作之一
This is Baltimore Bob's one of a kind creation.
受到了中国太阳能
Inspired by the Chinese Solar
温室设计的启发 用二氧化碳促进光合作用
greenhouse designs with CO2 enrichment.
不需要杀虫剂 不使用化肥
Pesticide free, and totally 100% organic.
这是我们生产乙醇的地方
This is where we make the ethanol,
鲍勃一直在调试
and Bob is constantly tinkering with the recipe
生产高辛烷值燃油的配方
to deliver a high-octane brew.
我们自己生产的是墙外送来
It's got 20 times more kick than the
经过稀释的燃油效用的二十倍
water downed petrol from outside the wall.
他就等于是混乱王国的石油供应商
He is like the OPEC of the Sprawl.
他不受弗兰克的支配吗
And he is not in Frank's pocket?
他们安排好了的
They have an arrangement.
他提供燃油 作为交换 弗兰克
He provides fuel, and Frank...
为他提供保护 还给一些其他的好处
reciprocate with some protection and a few other perks.
我们比其他人吃的食物要好一些
We eat a little bit better than the rest.
你考虑过了吗
You slept on it?
我考虑过了
I did.
就算你懂这方面的技巧
Let's say you have the skills.
参加死亡飞车的都是精神病和杀手
Death race is for sociopaths, the killers.
隆隆的轰鸣声会震撼你的五脏六腑
You gotta have grumble in your guts.
你的周围会弥漫着
You have to live for the smell of,
润滑油和优质燃油的味道
motor oil and high octane fuel.
你会爱上轮胎和沥青路面的摩擦声
You gotta love the sound of rubber on asphalt
还有你嘴里的血腥味
and taste of blood in your mouth.
当你晚上睡着的时候 我是说睡的非常沉的时候
And when you go to sleep at night, I mean that deep real sleep,
子弹划破空气声音才会让你感到一丝慰藉
the sound of bullets wheezing past your head should give you comfort.
所以这位强壮而沉静的先生
So, Mr. Strong and Silent,
你水平过硬吗
you made of that stuff?
如果不过硬 那我就死了 对吧
If I'm not, then I die, right?
所以你想试一试
So you want a shot?
我让你试一试
I'm getting you a shot.
就在今晚
Tonight.
死亡之坑
Death Pit.
准备战斗
Be ready to fight!
欢迎来到死亡之坑 你们这帮罪恶的囚犯
Welcome to the Dead Pit, your degenerate convicts.
今晚"你死我活"的决赛 应该是最为血腥的
Tonight the final death match promises to be the bloodiest one yet.
屠杀要开始了
The carnage is about to begin.
所以请各位就座 准备欣赏最为狂野的比赛吧
So take your seat and get ready for the wildest ride yet.
什么事
Hello?
你好 老朋友
Hi, old friend.
百事通 伙计 有什么事找我吗
Lists, my buddy, what do you got for me?
来了一个新家伙
There is a new guy.
这是他第一次参加"你死我活"比赛
This is his first death match,
但巴尔的摩·鲍勃说 他很能打
but Baltimore Bob says, he can fight.
他可能会是弗兰克的挑战者
He could be a challenger.
他什么来头
What's his story?
康纳·吉布森
Connor Gibson,
因为某项重罪进来的
in for felony whatever.
两项罪名 六项罪名 谁在乎呢
Two counts, six counts, who's counting?
反正和大家一样关在这里
He is in here with the rest of us.
我真希望能给你多介绍一些他的情况
I wish I had a few more bullet points for you but
但他这个人身上疑点重重
he is a question mark.
你直接把信息发给我吧
Why don't you send me the link,
我会自己去调查一下的
and I'll... Uh check him out.
等下 还有一件事
Wait. Before you go,
我们汽车零件 弹药 CAT5网络缆线短缺
we are running short on spare parts, bulk ammo, CAT 5 cable.
能不能给我们弄些进来
Could you hook me up?
- 下次送货的时候给你们送过去 - 再见 朋友
- It will be on the next shipment. - Adios Amigo!
来吧 看看这家伙几斤几两
Okay, let's see what this kid's made of.
监狱长 来看一下
Warden, check it out.
有什么情况
What do you have?
他们正在电视广播死亡之坑的情况
They are transmitting the telecast from the death pit.
是"你死我活"的决赛
It's the final death match.
欢迎观看"你死我活"的决赛
Welcome to the final death match.
比赛内容非常简单
This one is simple easy.
比赛的名字叫做"抢到钥匙" 规则如下
It's called  "Capture the Keys". Here is the rules.
我们来这不是看什么打倒人的狗屁拳击比赛
We are not here to see some MMA submission bullshit.
而是来欣赏骨头粉碎
We are here to see bone blasting.
脊椎断裂的乐趣的
Spine shattering fun.
重点是杀戮
It's about kill.
刀刀见血 刀刀见骨
It's about blood... And bone.
这还会引用别人说的话啊
Oh man, somebody's gonna get a citation.
观众来这不是看胆小鬼拍地认输的
We are not here to see some fucking pussy tap out.
那个拿到那串钥匙的人
The one person who gets that set of keys.
用钥匙发动那辆车
And sticks it in the ignition of that car.
赢得死亡飞车比赛的最后席位
Wins the last spot in Death Race.
混蛋们 一路平安
Adios, suckers. Peace out.
来人叫报警啊
Somebody call the police!
他会是有力的挑战者 这么厉害的可不多见
He is a challenger. You can't teach that.
杀了那混蛋
Crush that motherfucker.
那小子挺能打的嘛
That pretty boy can fight!
是啊 但他会开车么
Yeah, but can he drive?
我倒想看看他开车像不像他打架一样厉害
Who cares, I want to know if he fucks like he fights.
撕碎那混蛋
Rip that motherfucker!
混蛋
Fuck.
先生们 女士们 让我们欢迎屠夫登场
Ladies and gentlemen, let's hear it for the butcher.
这位壮汉有多次击杀记录
This mountain human has a tally full of killing under his belt.
在击杀榜上记有67次击杀记录
Having chalked up 67 body bags on the kill board.
投降什么的可跟他搭不上边
Submission is not his thing.
祝你好运 康纳
Good luck out there, Connor.
你拿到了钥匙
You got the keys,
但你够胆么
do you have the balls?
跟你打个小赌 这小白脸撑不过一分钟
Side bet, this pretty boy doesn't last a minute.
我跟你赌
I will take that.
干掉他
Down goes Freezer!
- 我的天 - 难以置信
- Shit. - Unbelievable.
啊 让我感觉自己又充满活力了 混蛋
Ah! Made me feel young again. Shit!
我给你准备了一份大礼 弗兰克斯坦
I got something for you, Frankenstein.
给你准备了一份大礼 宝贝
Got something for you baby.
把胜利者叫过来谈谈
Bring the winner by for a talk.
乐意效劳
With pleasure.
这混蛋真厉害
That's a bad motherfucker.
你是现在就付
You wanna pay now or, or shall I
还是先赊着
throw up on the tab?
我现在就付
I'll pay now.
弗兰克觉得你可能想换一件新衬衫
Frank thought you might want a fresh shirt.
我觉得你可能想要我
I thought you might want me.
我可不喜欢色情影星
I'm not into porn stars.
你不会放弃这个大好机会的
You can't pass this up.
我会的
I can.
他恐怕是不行的
He might have something to say about that.
如果你觉得你能打败弗兰克斯坦
If you think you can make a go over against Frankenstein,
那你就错了
you're wrong.
我可比你有种多了 但我却只能勉强应付他
I can barely handle him and I am three times the man you are.
真没用
Pussy.
卡丽对你还算友好么
Was Carley hospitable?
还行吧
Something like that.
你给我留下了两次深刻印象
You have impressed me, twice.
想做到这样可不容易
That's not easily done.
你对混乱王国的第一印象是什么
What were your first impressions of the Sprawl?
一片混乱
Anarchy.
比外面的世界更混乱么
Any more than the outside world?
我是这么认为的
I think so.
要是你当上了这里的老大 你觉得你能应付的了么
Do you think you can handle being king of this mountain?
我只是来这比赛的
I'm just here to race.
是啊 但是如果你赢了呢 怎么办
Yes. But if you win? Then what?
你做好准备领导他们 做出艰难选择了么
Are you ready to lead? To make hard decisions?
混乱王国现在是自给自足 但是以前并非如此
The sprawl is self-sustaining, but it wasn't always this way.
我刚到的时候 这还是一片荒凉
When I arrived it was a wasteland.
维兰德国际说要将混乱王国
Weyland Corporation promote this Sprawl
打造成另类的监狱
as an alternative to regular prisons.
那就是一个谎言
That was a lie.
实际上 送到
The Sprawl was created
混乱王国的人 等于是判了死刑
as an alternative to the death penalty.
他们把奶酪扔进来 希望我们像老鼠一样互相争斗
They throw us cheese and expect us to act like rats.
他们并没有想到我们会发展起来
They did not expect us to evolve.
但我们现在正是如此 以后也是如此
But we are, and we will.
我让这个地方不再混乱
I keep this place from anarchy.
你说的这些 和这里的街头比赛有设么关系
What does this have to do with the street race?
那不只是街头比赛而已 我们本性如此
It's not just a street race, It is who we are.
你是什么人 康纳·吉布森
Who are you, Connor Gibson?
一位无名之辈罢了
Nobody special.
要是你赢下了死亡飞车 恐怕就不是如此了
Oh, that could change if you win Death Race,
如果你打败了我的话
if you defeat me.
为什么你会愿意冒丢失一切权力的风险呢
Why would you be willing to risk losing all this power?
死亡飞车给了所有人当上老大的机会
Death race gives anyone the opportunity to become king.
没有这一点激励着我们 我们将一事无成
Without that to inspire, we are nothing.
如果你赢了 你当上老大的第一件事是什么
If you win, what would be your first act as king?
我还没考虑过这个问题
I haven't really thought about it.
我之所以赢了 是因为我非常清楚
I won because I knew exactly
我成了老大之后 想干什么
what I wanted to do when I was king of this hill.
如果你不知道自己想要什么
If you don't know what you want,
那你就会死在赛道上
you will die on the track.
混乱王国会欢呼庆祝你的死亡
And the Sprawl would cheer your death.
所以关键的问题是
So the question is...
你到底想要什么
What do you want?
来啊 宝贝 上车
Come on baby, get in.
今晚真是疯狂
That was insane tonight.
不行 贝克丝
The answer is no, Bexie.
你还是别当死亡飞车比赛的领航员吧
You don't wanna ride shotgun in Death Race.
我一定要参加
Yes, I do.
那就跟判死刑没什么两样
It's a death sentence.
弗兰克杀了我在乎的人
Frank has killed people I cared about.
我也想出力把他干掉
I want to be part of putting him down.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
我觉得我们能一起喝一杯
I thought we could have a drink.
所以 梅丽是谁
So, who is Merry?
她是你最爱的时髦小妞
Is she your favorite groupie,
还是你特别爱过圣诞节
or you just really into Christmas?
那是我妹妹 梅雷迪思 的昵称
It's uh... My sister, Meredith.
我服役的时候她去世了
She died when I was in the service.
连跟她道别的机会都没有
Never got to say goodbye.
也无法挽回了
Can't change it, so...
看了不少 也干了不少坏事
Seen a lot of bad stuff. Done a lot of bad things.
梅丽是个好人
Merry was good.
比我好 这是肯定的
Better than me, that's for sure.
我
I was, uh...
我出生在小石城
I was born in, Little Rock.
我猜你爸爸信教吧
Son of a preacher man.
算不上信教
Hardly.
我爸是个汽车修理工 一身油污
My old man was a grease monkey in a pair of
他的乐趣就是坐在门廊上喝迪克西啤酒
His idea of a good time was drinking Dixie beer on the porch,
数着萤火虫
and, count the fireflies.
我小时候的大部分时间都呆在
Spent most of my young life in
德克萨斯 斯威特沃特的一个废品回收站
Sweet water, Texas, on a salvage yard.
梅丽是在长岛去世的
Merry, passed away in Long Beach.
所以我就搬去那儿了
So I ended up there.
好消息是
So, the good news is
V8标准变速器正常工作
the V8 standard transmission and it runs,
坏消息是需要换轮胎 刹车
but the bad news is that it needs tires, brakes
发动机要大修 需要燃料电池 装甲 需要武器
and toll engine over haul of it, fuel cell, armor, weapon needed
别扯这些了 百事通 重要的是 这车基本上什么部件都缺
Man, don't pull me with it, Lists. Bottom line, it needs everything.
这玩意是什么
What the hell is this thing?
后挡板
Your tombstone.
钛制防弹装甲 保护汽车的燃料电池
Bullet-proof titanium plate, protects your fuel cell.
你找到领航员了么
You got a navigator yet?
他有领航员的
Hell yeah, he does.
我他妈的坐前排
I'm the motherfucker riding shotgun.
你他妈的在看什么
The hell you looking at?
我脑子自带防冻剂的
I got anti freeze in my brains.
我们来造这玩意吧
Let's build this shit.
速度计上限已调整至200英里每小时了
The speedometer has been calibrated to 200 miles per hour.
它就这点本事了么
Is that all she's got?
我们来试试看
Let's find out.
死亡飞车比赛的第一天 绕赛道一圈
This Death race, is one lap, one day.
比赛的起点和终点都在飞机场
The race begins and ends at the airfield.
便于加速 障碍很少
Nice speed here, few obstacles.
比赛的第二天 在94号州际公路上
Second day, is on Interstate 94.
大部分车会在这一段长赛道上报废
Most of ballistic cars will be taken out on this long stretch here.
小心高速路匪帮 那是他们的地盘
Watch out for the highway gang, this is their turf.
然后 你就进入下一关"计划"
And then, you hit the projects.
那里是非常凶险的
All kind of bad boys' in there.
你要是活着从那边出来了
You come out of there alive,
就到了肉类包装区
you end up in the Meatpacking District?
就能轻松取胜了
Home free.
驾驶比杀戮更加重要
Driving is more important than killing.
必要的时候才开枪 思考要沉稳 驾驶要迅猛
Shoot only when you must. Think slow, drive fast.
规则一 保住你的小命
Rule no. 1, keep your ass alive.
你真是太猛了
That was incredible.
别他妈的碰我
Don't fucking touch me.
你好
Hi.
你喜欢车么
So you like cars?
喜欢
Yeah.
我喜欢美国肌肉车
I like American muscle.
我有辆车
I had a Vett.
自己改装了一下
Rebuilt it myself.
1970产LT-1引擎
A 1970 LT-1.
很不错啊
Sting ray.
原来很喜欢开着车去拉斯维加斯 在高速上狂奔
Used to love the opener upon highway to Vegas.
油门踩到底 370马力
Paddle to the floor, 370 horses running hard.
霍利&罗切斯特四喉管式化油器
Holley and Rochester Quadrajet Carb
让燃气比恰到好处
getting the mixture just right.
冲力转换
Momentum shift,
别踩刹车 控制稳了
stay off the brakes, get her on her toes.
我的天 要是它会飞就好了
Man, could she fly.
你跟你认识的每个女孩都这样聊天么
How about you talk like this to all your girls?
我在墙外的世界也是一无所有
I got nothing outside these walls.
梅丽是我同那个世界最后的联系
Merry was my last connection to anything real.
所以她去世之后
So when she died
我做了一个非常糟糕的决定
I made a bad decision.
最后进了这里 我什么事什么人都不在乎了
Wind up here, not caring 'bout anything or anyone.{
但是现在
But now...
But now?
我们来找你了
We come for you!
吉布森中士
Sergeant Gibson.
已经很久没有人这么叫过我了
No one has called me that in a long time.
康纳·吉布森 并非我们所认为的那种人
Connor Gibson, is not the man we're coming to know.
他是一位勇士
He is a warrior.
是一位受勋无数 本领高超的勇士
A very decorated and specialized warrior.
因为他为中情局所执行的黑色行动
Known in the shadow world of government
在邪恶的政府界很有名气
killers for his wet work in the CIA.
杀戮目标人物是他的专长 我就是他的目标
Target and killing is his forte, and I am his mark.
他是遵照维兰德国际的命令来到这里
He is here at the behest of Weyland International.
外面的法西斯分子把他派他过来
Sent here by the fascist from the outside,
因为他们觉得我力量太强大了
because they think I've gained too much power.
他就是政府的走狗
They fitted him with a strap,
政府手里的工具
and he hangs around their waist like a hatchet.
终点线会有一架直升机
There is a helicopter ride to freedom,
把你救出去
waiting for him at the finish line.
告诉我 中士
Tell me Sergeant,
我有没有说错
am I wrong?
杀了他
Kill! Kill!
Kill him!
吉布森中士
Sergeant Gibson...
叛徒
Betrayer!
允许他参加比赛
Will be allowed to race.
去他妈的 弗兰克 要是他赢了呢
Fuck that Frank? What if he wins?
那他就赢了 这也正是他来的目的
Then he wins! And that his words meant to be.
你是觉得我发现不了吗
Did you think I woudn't find out?
现在告诉我 谁才是藏在面具背后的人
So tell me, who's hiding behind a mask now?
我还是你
Me or you?
我们起点线见
See you on the starting line.
这是真的么
Is it true?
再见 长岛小子
Goodbye, Long Beach.
简 求你别走
Jane please.
把你的手从我身上拿开
Get your goddamn hands off me!
我还是会给你的车做后勤维护的
I am still one of your pit crew.
我不在乎他们是不是送你进来杀掉弗兰克
I don't care if they have sent you to kill him or not.
他是个骗子 鲍勃
He's a liar, Bob!
为那些达官贵人效劳的
A liar who is working for the
嘿 别说了
Hey, get over it.
他干这行很厉害
He is good for business.
我们得准备好参加比赛
We got a race to get ready for.
头脑保持清醒 犯人
Get your head right, convict.
你的生死存亡取决于此
Your life depends on it.
比赛日 真是漫长啊
We got a long race day... Huh?
准备好了么 混蛋
Are you ready, mother fucker?
我听不见你们 你们这帮娘炮
I can't hear you, you fucking pussies!
选手来了
Here they are!
欢迎观看死亡飞车 终极汽车厮杀比赛
Welcome to Death Race, the ultimate auto carnage.
比赛一天 十一位选手
One day, eleven drivers,
共有四个关卡 250台摄像机同步直播
four stages, and over 250 live cameras...
进展顺利呢 瓦伦丁先生
Just like clockwork, Mr. Valentine.
这是你最后的机会 要么弗兰克斯坦死 要么你前途完蛋
This is it, last chance. Frankenstein dies or your career dies.
今天晚些时候 弗兰克斯坦会进尸体袋的
Frankenstein will be in a body bag by day's end.
为了你的前途 我希望结局最好如此
I hope so for your sake.
我现在介绍一下参加本次比赛的男女们吧
Now talk about the bad boys and girls who run this race.
参加了三次比赛的约翰尼·条子 座驾是怪兽警车
Featuring 3 time racer Johnny Law and his monster police cruiser.
他是来保护大家 为大家服务的
He is here to protect and serve.
早上好 混蛋们
Morning, motherfuckers.
火焰男 参加过两次比赛 座驾是道奇公羊
Two time racer, the Fireman, and his Dodge Ram Hemi.
他的车要驶过你们面前了
His ass is coming through your door.
快来给妈妈我一些爱
Come show momma some love.
女王 玛蒂尔达
The Queen, Matilda The Hun,
座驾是黄色伊克诺莱恩校车
boarding her school bus yellow econoline van.
首次参加比赛的吉普赛·萝丝 座驾是迷你库珀
And first timer Gipsy Rose and her bad ass mini cooper S.
恐怕只有他妈妈才会愿意瞧他的脸了
With a face only a mother could love,
这位是刺猬脸 座驾是大众甲壳虫
here's Pierced-Face and his VW bug.
这位是纳粹混蛋 座驾是地狱嗜血卡车
Nazi Bastard and his bloodthirsty truck from hell.
这位是战争循环 座驾是一级方程式赛车
Dirt and his Formula 1 War Cycle,
开得快才能活命
counting on speed to keep him alive.
"活死人"也是老选手了 座驾是"赫克杀手"
Veteran Racer Dead man and his killer hurk.
他可不是来这送死的
He didn't come here to rest in peace.
这位的座驾是丰田赛利卡
Behind the wheel of her Toyota Celica,
处女赛车手克利奥帕特拉
virgin racer Cleopatra.
最后一位
And last, but definitely least,
我们这儿的内奸 吉布森中士 座驾是雪佛兰科迈罗
Our resident rat fuck, Sergeant Gibson and his Camero.
他可是全场人的靶子哟
He has got bulls-eye on his back.
准备好开始咱们的第一次约会么
You ready for our play date?
全场的人都要来杀你了 我的搭档
You got the whole world coming after you my man,
你应该知道这个吧
you know that right?
你走吧 贝克丝 我自己可以的
Take a walk Bexie, I got this.
我是应该这样的
I should.
你是好是坏由不得我来评说
Who am I to judge?
我不是来批评你的
I ain't here to throw shade on you.
你这么做固然有自己的理由
You surely got reasons.
所以咱们说清楚了 我会跟你一起参加比赛的
So, if it's all the same, I'll ride with you.
现在欢迎我们的冠军
Now, give it up for your champion,
赛场归来 七连胜
returning to track after seven straight win,
不死之人
the man who just won't die...
弗兰克斯坦
Frankenstein!
弗兰克 亲爱的
Frank, baby!
有时候我有一种这样的感觉 弗兰克是在下棋
Sometimes I get the feeling, Frank is playing chess.
而我们这些人都是棋子
And the rest of us are playing checkers.
让她走吧 弗兰克
Let her go, Frank.
她和我们之间的事没有关系
She's got nothing to do with any of this.
确实没有
No,
但她确实能给我提供很不错的保障
but she's a good insurance policy.
让我们看看 你有多冷血吧
Let's see how cold-blooded you are.
送她上车
Put her in the car.
欢迎观看死亡飞车比赛
Welcome to Death Race,
有五千四百万观众 正在暗网上
streaming live on the dark web to over 54 million viewers
通过250部摄像头实况直播
on 250 live camera feeds.
这是终极汽车厮杀比赛 未经剪辑 原始狂野
This is the ultimate vehicular carnage, uncut and totally raw.
第一关 飞机场
Stage one, The airfield.
这胸真假
Fake tits.
比赛结束了真应该好好上她
We should fuck her after the race.
准备大干一场
Let's light this fire.
现在回去 在椅子上
Now go back, and strap your sweet
乖乖坐好
little ass in that chair girl.
哈哈 来吧
Ha-ha! Come on!
伙计 躁动起来吧
Dude, let's get this party started!
一辆挂了 还有十辆
One down, ten to go!
今天咱们赚的估计是最多的了
This is gonna be the biggest payday ever.
贝克丝 帮我个忙
Hey Bexie, do me a favor and
让那些混蛋别跟在我屁股后面了
get those motherfuckers off my ass.
那我们开炸吧
Let's blast some shit up!
给我找人 想办法联系到
Find me someone who can give me
康纳·吉布森
some access on Connor Gibson.
告诉他 我全押他赢了
And tell him I'm all in.
还有九名车手在死亡赛道上
Nine drivers remain here on the Dead lands.
弗兰克斯坦 康纳·吉布森和吉普赛·萝丝目前领先
Frankenstein, Connor Gibson and Gipsy Rose, lead the path.
系好安全带 婊子们 柏油路已经发红了
Buckle up, bitches, the asphalt is running red,
我们这只是热身而已
and we are just getting warmed up.
第二关 死亡之地
Stage two, The dead lands.
你完蛋了 你个混蛋
You're going down, you sodomite motherfucker!
把他干掉
Take him out!
去你的 火焰男
Fuck you, Fireman!
那婊子死的真可惜啊
Now that's a waste of some good pussy!
我想不出还有什么更好的表达方式了
I couldn't have said it better myself.
咱们的老大 弗兰克斯坦
Frankenstein and the Benedict Arnold himself,
在和康纳·吉布森竞争头名
Connor Gibson, battle for the lead.
吉普赛·萝丝 和 约翰尼·条子 排在前面
Gipsy Rose and Johnny Law hanging around the front of the path.
我们送弗兰克上西天吧
Let's put Frank in a body bag once and for all.
导弹准备
Arming missiles.
让我们看看你男朋友是否下得了手杀你
Let's see if your boyfriend's ready to bury you.
别开火
Don't do it.
别想她了 康纳 那个瘦婊子再也不会回到你身边了
Let her go, Connor. That skinny bitch ain't never coming back.
我说了 别开火
I said, don't do it.
我就知道
Just what I thought.
去他妈的死鬼
Fucking Los Muertos.
混蛋
Fuck!
尝尝这个
Suck on this!
小朋友们 抱紧你们的泰迪
Hold onto your teddies, bitches!
还有六名车手
Six Death Racers left.
- 继续 - 我们走
- Go ahead! - Let's go!
谁他妈的开一辆大众巴士参加死亡飞车比赛啊
Who the hell brings a VW bus in a Death Race?
那你得问这些人渣们了
You gotta hand it to these degenerates.
他们演的真是一场好戏
They put on a hell of a show.
我们的后挡板快撑不住了
Our tombstone can't hold out much longer.
谁打个911啊
Somebody call the 911!
甩掉这个疯子
Lose this psychopath.
混蛋 你没打中
Missed motherfucker!
开始钓鱼
Fish on!
我们被勾住了
We are hooked.
别急 贝克丝 我有个办法了
Hang on, Bexie, I got an idea.
你想干什么呢 混蛋
What are you doing, motherfucker?
鱼儿 鱼儿
Yeah, fishy fishy.
出来玩吧
Come out and play.
混蛋 这个内奸和他的婊子贝克丝
Fuck me, this traitor and his bitch, Bexie,
刚刚把火焰男烧死了
just burnt down the Fireman.
看来只有五位车手进入了下一关"计划"
Only five Death Racers left to seem heading to the Projects.
弗兰克斯坦仍在最前 吉普赛·萝丝紧随其后 位居第二
Frankenstein is still in the lead, with Gipsy Rose up close second,
康纳·吉布森在最后一名
And Conor Gibson is behind everyone's dust, dead last.
第三关 计划
Stage three, the Project.
他妈的死亡飞车
Fucking Death Race!
嘿 你
Hey, you!
这是你干的吗
Did you do this?
不 是我们干的
No, we did!
我已经在这等你很久了
Just the man I was gunning for.
别来无恙啊
How you doing, Wonder Bread?
你这混蛋
You stupid motherfucker!
去你妈的
Fick ditch, Schwarzer!
我的天 他说什么
Oh, no, he didn't?
他刚刚是不是说了 我认为他会说的那些话
Did he just say what I think he said?
是的 但是用德语说的
Yeah, but in German.
你和你的婊子 开着你们的破车
You and your bitch, brought your shit,
走错了路
to the wrong part of town.
准备开打吧
Get ready to play.
我们得让他改变路线 走桥上
We gotta re-route him over the bridge.
要想赢得比赛 他这绕的太远了
He is too far out to win this race.
我才不跟他通话呢
I'm not telling him.
给我联系他
Get him on line.
说吧 鲍勃
Talk to me Bob.
你得改变路线 走桥上
We need to re-route you over the bridge.
桥已经断了
The bridge is out.
你他妈为什么要让我走那里
Why the fuck you re routing me there?
你落后太多了 你必须跃过那条沟
You are too far behind, You have to jump the gap.
距离多长 50英尺
What are we talking about, like 50 feet?
差不多250英尺
More like 250 feet.
如果你想赢 那是你唯一的机会
That's your only chance if you wanna win.
我必须要赢
I have to win.
没人会为一个纳粹混蛋和他那可憎的女人喝彩
No one's gonna cite a cheer for Nazi Bastard and his nasty little Fraulein.
我的意思是 这对我们来说不算是个损失
I mean, hu hu, it's not a real loss to the planet earth.
剩下四名车手
Four drivers remain.
弗兰克斯坦和吉普赛·萝丝远远领先于
Frankenstein and Gipsy Rose taken up a big lead
约翰尼·条子 和 康纳·吉布森
on Johnny Law and Connor Gibson.
那么 我们该怎么做呢 鲍勃
So, how do we do this, Bob?
你必须以每小时220英里的时速冲过那条沟
You gotta hit the gap at 220 miles an hour.
那儿有一个斜坡
There is a ramp there.
这已经不是第一次有人尝试这么做了
Not the first time this has been tried.
不行 我们只能最高达到每小时200英里
No, we are only calibrated to 200 miles an hour.
别担心 应该能达到220的
Don't worry, should get you up to 220.
以前有人成功冲过去么
Anyone ever made this jump before?
理论上来说 是可以的
On paper, the math works.
下落的时候情况如何
What about the landing?
跟你实话实说 那不会容易的
I ain't gonna lie to you, it's gonna be a hard one.
如果你的角度正确 你可能会活下来
If you get your angle right, you might live.
好吧 他妈的真是谢谢你了
Yeah, fuck you very much.
那个该死的内奸追上来了
That rat fuck is back.
你这朋克婊子
Punk ass bitch!
这招挺有效的
That worked well.
好
Yeah!
好吧 我们来搞定这事
Okay! Let's get this done already.
下个路口左转 这座桥离你五英里远
To your next left, the bridge is five miles out.
这是你唯一的机会
This is your only chance.
你喜欢这场表演吗 鲍勃
You like this play, Bob?
这是你唯一的表演了
It's your only play.
我会在另一边见你
I'll see you on the other side.
你应该下车的 贝克丝
You should get out, Bexie.
我们无路可走了
We are at end of the road.
没他妈的门儿
Not fucking happening.
上这辆车的时候 我就把一切都赌进去了
The minute I got in this car with you, I was all in.
所以我们开干吧
So let's do this.
这只是重力的问题
It's just gravity.
我们最高时速是209
We maxed it out at 209.
我在把后挡板卸下来
I'm dropping the tombstone.
加油 冲
Come on! Come on!
好
Yes!
好 好 好
Yes! Yes! Yes!
我说了 理论上是可以的
I told you the math worked.
我现在就想给你口了
I could suck you off right now.
刚才看到的 简直难以置信
I can't believe what I just saw.
康纳·吉布森跃过了桥 从右后方跟了上来
Connor Gibson jumped the bridge cutting in right back in
这混蛋真有一套
Motherfucker got game.
来吧 别让我失望
Come on, don't let me down.
你必须赢得这场比赛
You have got to win this race.
你男朋友来了
Here comes your boyfriend.
贝克丝 给我接通弗兰克
Bex, patch me through to Frank.
嘿 弗兰克
Hey Frankie.
嘿 康纳 很高兴你能来赴你的命运之约
Hey, Connor, glad you show up for your date with destiny.
我就知道这事会发生在我们俩身上
I knew it would come down to us.
我也没有别的办法了
I wouldn't have it any other way.
我们可以开枪对射 或者赛车
We can start shooting at each other, or we can drive.
你想选哪个
What do you prefer?
我们赛车吧
Let's drive.
第四关 肉类包装区
Stage four, meat packing district.
拜托 我们快没时间了 快解决掉他
C'mon! We are running out of time, take him out already.
怎么了
What's going on?
他的燃料电池耗尽了
His fuel cell is empty.
搞什么啊 开快点啊 康纳
What the fuck? Drive, Connor!
我们没油了
We are out of gas.
燃油管断裂了
The fuel line is ruptured.
不要这样做 你
Don't do it. Just...
掉头走人 赢下比赛就好
Turn around and win your race.
这是死亡飞车比赛 他必须死
This is Death Race. He has to die.
他明白的
He knows it.
这是他的选择
He chose it.
太好了
Alright!
那是我们的人 派直升机过去
That's our queue, send in the chopper.
已经在路上了
It's already on route.
滚远点
Get the fuck outta here.
我来救你了 简
I got you, I got you, Jane.
终止我们在暗网的直播
Jam the broadcast to the dark web.
但是 现在正是精彩的时候
But, this is good stuff...
按我说的做 切断5分钟
Just do it! Cut it for five minutes.
糟了
Oh shit.
这才是监狱长想要的
This is what the warden wants.
他想让弗兰克死在公众面前
He wants Frank's death on display.
要是让他得逞 我们就会输
We give it to him, we'll lose.
去他妈的
Fuck him.
搞定了 我们走吧
The job's done, let's go!
慢着
Hold on.
他们派我们两个一起来的
They send two of us?
为了保险
Insurance.
干的很好 是吧
Pretty well, huh?
谢谢你的帮忙
And thanks for the assist.
每个人都太关注你了 我才有机会赶过来
Everyone was so focused on you, I flew under the radar.
我们赶紧离开这该死的鬼地方吧
Let's get the fuck out of this shit hole.
弗兰克斯坦死了 干的漂亮
Frankenstein is dead, job well done.
哦 顺便说一下
Oh and by the way...
我们现在两清了
We are all square now.
20秒钟后我就离开
20 seconds and I'm gone.
康纳 听好了
Connor, listen up.
戴上面具 你就是弗兰克斯坦
Put on the mask, become Frankenstein.
混乱王国 永远不会追随康纳·吉布森
The sprawl, will never follow Connor Gibson.
他们追随的是弗兰克斯坦
They follow Frankenstein.
没有他的话
Without him,
一片混乱
chaos.
让我们结束这场比赛吧 长岛小子
Let's finish this race, Long Beach.
现在 继续直播死亡飞车
Now, put Death Race, back on live.
金伯格肯定会气死的
Goldberg is gonna be pissed.
他往康纳身上赌了太多钱
He put heavy action on Connor.
赢钱容易 输钱也容易
Easily come, easy go.
去你妈的 瓦伦丁
Fuck you, Valentine.